In January of 2026, the 41st single of Nojizaka46 was announced.
Today, the 41st single of Nojizaka46 was announced.
16 members of the 41st single were selected.
The formation is 7 people in the back row, 6 people in the middle row, and 3 people in the front row.
The 41st single of this center is Teresa Ikeda.
Teresa Ikeda.
That's it for the 41st single.
The center is Teresa Ikeda.
And as it was announced, the under-member formation was announced.
From this time on, 6 members will also participate as under-members.
No. 17, Hina Kawabata.
No. 15, Mirine Masuda.
No. 9, Urumi Morihira.
The 6 members' names are called one by one.
And...
The under-center of the 41st single in the front row is Hina Okamoto.
The under-center is Hina Okamoto.
That's it for the 41st single of the under-member formation.
The day of the under-live was also announced.
The under-live will be held in March.
The day of the under-live will be held in March.
No one knew what kind of live it would be.
This is bad.
In this under-live, 10 members of the 6th generation will mix with their seniors.
Let's go.
All of them had the formation number of No. 46.
They had the formation number of No. 46 as a group.
The waiting room.
They remembered something there.
It's again.
Yes.
It's Pia Arena again.
Yes, it's Pia Arena again.
The stage of the Pia Arena MM was the stage where they stood for the first time.
It feels like we're back.
It's true.
Let's do our best.
Everyone is strong.
They're seniors.
That's right.
What they have to learn.
What they have to learn from their seniors.
They don't do anything.
We'll be back.
Nice to meet you.
Good evening, everyone.
We're the 6th generation of Nogizaka 46.
Nice to meet you.
A few days before the rehearsal of the under-live
The 6th generation were standing on the stage of the 5th album, Memorial Live My Respect.
They weren't 10 people.
And as we announced on the Nogizaka46 official website
The 6th generation member, Mitsuki-chan, was unwell and was unable to perform today.
Even if Mitsuki is sick, the 6th generation of Nogizaka46 will do her best
So please take care of us until the end.
Please take care of us.
Setoguchi was absent from the rehearsal.
Yada was a double center at Biriyani.
She talked about this after the live.
I felt Mitsuki.
I thought there was another person.
I thought about Mitsuki's part.
I think she was the most frustrated.
I thought about it.
Everyone thought the same about Setoguchi's part.
But the truth is, I would be happier if Setoguchi was there.
The first day of the under-live rehearsal.
There was someone waiting.
There was.
The 6th generation of Nogizaka46 entered the rehearsal several hours earlier than their seniors.
Most of them performed for the first time.
They had to practice in advance.
There are a lot of things to remember.
I think it's good to be in the original position this time.
That's right.
I'm really desperate to keep up.
Once you start to lose your mind, you'll lose it.
I'm so excited.
But I think I'm getting more and more focused.
I was focused on the first hour of the lesson.
But today, there were 4 songs.
I think it's natural.
I thought it was amazing.
It's amazing.
I do feel like I'm getting better.
But...
I thought I was getting better.
But I'm desperate to keep up with my seniors.
I want to practice more and more.
I want to practice a lot by myself.
They know that there are things that can be done and things that can't be done.
The 41st single, Under Live.
In this documentary, we will show the lives of the 6th generation students and seniors.
We will show them in real time.
Next time, a full-fledged rehearsal.
A part of the performance's song.